Young Women's Christian Association of Greater Hartford Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Young Women's Christian Association of Greater Hartford Records.
undated, 1867-1988.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Center.
Young Women's Christian Association of Greater Hartford.
23 linear feet.
MSS19910024
At the time of its formation in 1866, the Hartford Association was one of the earliest Associations for young women in America, and the first community social agency in Hartford.
History
At the time of its formation in 1866, the Hartford Association was one of the earliest Associations for young women in America, and the first community social agency in Hartford. In 1867, the Association was incorporated as The Women's Christian Association, with rooms for rent at two adjacent Hartford locations. These boarding facilities for young women were to be self-supporting and offer “most of the advantages of a well-ordered Christian home at much less price than a common boarding house.” The rooms were open every day and evening “for social purposes, reading, Bible and singing classes.” In an effort to provide further support to its residents, an employment service was established.
In 1889, an education program was formed with classes in typing, stenography, bookkeeping, penmanship, and grammar, along with a health education program offering classes in first aid, hygiene, and physical culture. In an effort to broaden its reach, a Group Work program was established in 1899 to offer the services of the Association to girls of the general community rather than only to those in the residence and workshop. Around 1912, with an expanding demand on the Association facilities, a site at Ann and Church Streets was purchased, a building campaign was launched, and, in 1916 a new building was erected. In 1926, Camp Aya-Po in Somers, Connecticut, was added to the Association's facilities. The same year, the Association changed its name to the Young Women's Christian Association and the personal basis of membership was adopted to replace the Protestant Evangelical membership requirement.
Throughout the 1940s, the YWCA continued to expand its services, acquiring space in West Hartford, Windsor and Wethersfield. In 1966, it was decided that the YWCA of Hartford County and the YWCA of Greater Hartford should unite to form one organization, allowing service expansion throughout the metropolitan area, and greater access to services for area residents.
During the 1970s and 1980s, YWCA programs changed and expanded to reflect the changing needs of women in Connecticut. While continuing to offer courses and counseling in career services, child care and physical fitness, a Jobs Corps program focused on employment and job training was establishment to meet the needs and demands of women moving from the home into the workplace. Programs in rape crisis, sexual assault crisis, sex equity, child abuse and women in leadership were established. The needs of a growing senior citizenry were addressed with a Senior Service program, Widow-to-Widow, and Neighborcare, while programs for teens were enlarged to encompass teens as parents, summer youth employment training and career exploration.
As part of its sense of global responsibility toward all women, the YWCA of Greater Hartford took part in a national boycott of the Nestlé Corporation from 1978 to 1981 in order to bring attention to advertising tactics throughout third world countries, which contributed to placing infants at risk from contaminated formula.
Scope and Content
The records of the YWCA of Greater Hartford document its growth and evolution as a service organization for women from its inception in 1866 through the early 1980s. The collection includes administrative and financial records, minutes, correspondence, publications, reports, newspaper clippings, memorabilia, 16mm film, negatives, photographs, a record album and scrapbooks.
Arrangement
Series I: Administrative Records ( 1867-1988 ) consists of files including reports of annual meetings, audits, budgets, outreach and service information, goals and objectives, and personnel and staff records. The series is further divided into eight subseries: Administrative, Branch, Historical, Finance, Statistics, Public Relations, Fund Raising, and Building Campaigns. The subseries Branch contains material on the various YWCA branches in the Greater Hartford area. Historical contains residence records, correspondence, photographic negatives, historical data, and printed materials from the late 1800s through the late 1950s. Finance consists of a cash book, committee reports, and a ledger book. The cash and ledger books cover the years 1870-1900. Statistics (1955-1985) contains local and national figures compiled by the YWCA on residence, membership, services and programs. Public Relations contains printed materials such as brochures, catalogs, program listings, events programs, forms, newsletters, news releases and newspaper clippings. The subseries also includes copies of the YWCA Triangle and a 45 rpm record of a service spot, “Women on the Move,” recorded by Gloria Steinem. Fund Raising consists of information on campaigns, promotional materials, benefits, foundations and scholarships. Building Campaigns contains material directly related to efforts on behalf of the YWCA to organize plans and raise funds for new construction.
Series II: Minutes ( undated, 1867-1985 ) contains records of business conducted by various committees; included are the Board of Directors, Executive, Finance, Human Resource, Steering, Public Affairs and Race Relations committees.
Series III: Committees ( undated, 1965-1987 ) consists of the records of YWCA committees. The series includes groups concerned with such issues as affirmative action, building and property, development, finance, planning, membership, public policy, and women's issues.
Series IV: Residence Records ( undated, 1967-1982 ) contains the records of YWCA rooming facilities. The series includes financial and managerial records, as well as correspondence and information on specific residences such as Ann Street and Woolverton Hall.
Series V: Camp Aya-Po ( undated, 1926-1984 ) records the physical and business management of the summer camp. Topics include a history, campsite information, physical plant information, use study and long range planning.
Series VI: Programs ( undated, 1967-1987 ) details the programs, services and events offered by the YWCA throughout the 1970s and 1908s. Subjects include career services, child care, fitness, youth programs, job corps, rape crisis, senior service, sex equity and women in leadership.
Series VII: Grants and Contracts ( undated, 1945-1987 ) consists of records concerning the acquisition and use of grant monies for YWCA services to the public. The majority of the grants target employment, training, and human resources.
Series VIII: World Mutual Services ( 1970-1982 ) contains information on the YWCA's involvement with and commitment to the Nestlé boycott. Included are correspondence endorsements, films, publicity and World Mutual Service Committee material.
Series IX: Films ( undated, 1969-1976 ) contains reels of 16mm film documenting YWCA events such as the 100th Anniversary Dinner. There is a WFSB-TV service spot and a film on women's activities and teen services.
Series X: Scrapbooks ( 1912-1983 ) is largely a collection of newspaper clippings, photographs and printed memorabilia. Many of the scrapbooks are specific to YWCA facilities, such as Camp Aya-Po and Old Woolverton Hall, or to YWCA groups, such as the Newcomers Club and Welcome Wagon.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut history and organizations. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
YWCA of Greater Hartford--History.; Women--Connecticut--Societies and clubs.; Young Women's Christian associations--Connecticut.; Young women--Connecticut--Religious life.; Hartford (Conn.)--Societies, etc.--YMCAs-YWCAs.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Photocopies.; Notes.; Scrap-Books.; Album.; Motion picture film.
Occupations:
Service organization.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to the University of Connecticut in the fall of 1989.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1867-1988
  - Subseries A: Administrative, undated, 1868-1987
    - Act of Incorporation, undated (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Action Audit, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - Action Audit: final report, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Affirmative Action, 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 4-5)
    - Affirmative Action, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - Action Action trainees, 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
    - Agency overview, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Anniversaries and events, undated (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Annual meeting
      - 1952 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
      - 1956 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
      - 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
      - 1964 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
      - 1967 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
      - 1968-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
      - 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
      - 1980 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
      - 1982 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Annual reports
      - 1868-1894 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
      - 1869 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
      - 1898-1916 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
      - 1900 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
      - 1911-1914 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
      - 1916-1918 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
      - 1921-1924, 1926 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
      - 1927-1931 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
      - 1931-1939 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
      - 1950, 1953, 1954, 1956, 1957, 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
      - 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 30-31)
      - 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
      - 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
      - 1976 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
      - 1977 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
      - 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
      - 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
      - 1980-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
    - Annual report to President and Executive Director, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 39)
    - Association review, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
    - Avery gifts, undated (Box 1:, Folder 41)
    - Board of Directors, 1976 (Box 1:, Folder 42)
    - Board of Directors, 1978-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 43)
    - Board of Directors, 1980-1982 (Box 1:, Folder 44)
    - Board members: installation, 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 46)
    - Budget proposal, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
    - Campaigns, 1916-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 48)
    - Camperships: Hartford Foundation for Public Service, 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 49)
    - Campership Program, 1983 (Box 1:, Folder 50)
    - Campership Program, 1984 (Box 1:, Folder 51)
    - Centennial, 1955 (Box 2:, Folder 52-53)
    - Centennial observance, 1968 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
    - Code of Personal Commitment, 1962 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
    - Community Chest, 1969-1970 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
    - Communications, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 57)
    - Connecticut Architect, undated (Box 2:, Folder 58)
    - Connecticut Communication Network, undated (Box 2:, Folder 59)
    - Connecticut Council of YWCA's, undated (Box 2:, Folder 60)
    - Consolidation, 1966 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
    - Constitution, undated (Box 2:, Folder 62)
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1871-1957 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
    - Description of services, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
    - Eatery, undated (Box 2:, Folder 65)
    - Emergency and first aid information, undated (Box 2:, Folder 66)
    - Executive Director's resignation, 1987 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
    - Farm Workers Council, undated (Box 2:, Folder 68)
    - Financial Procedures, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder 69)
    - Financial statement, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder 70)
    - Fire evacuation, undated (Box 2:, Folder 71)
    - Goals and objectives, 1979-1981 (Box 2:, Folder 72)
    - Goals and priorities, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 73)
    - Gonfalon contest, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 74)
    - Hartford YM/YWCA Building Fund Campaign, 1957 (Box 2:, Folder 75)
    - Human resources, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 76)
    - Joint facilities, undated (Box 2:, Folder 77)
    - Joint YM/YWCA—Greater Hartford, undated (Box 2:, Folder 78)
    - Joint YM/YWCA—West Hartford, undated (Box 2:, Folder 79)
    - Market research, undated (Box 2:, Folder 80)
    - Membership drive, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 81)
    - Merger, 1966 (Box 2:, Folder 82-83)
    - Metropolitan District building, undated (Box 2:, Folder 84-85)
    - National Association Review Team report, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder 86)
    - National Conventions
      - 1964 (Box 2:, Folder 87)
      - 1970 (Box 2:, Folder 88)
      - 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 89)
      - 1976 (Box 2:, Folder 90)
      - 1985 (Box 2:, Folder 91)
    - National support, undated (Box 2:, Folder 92)
    - Office procedures, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 93)
    - “135 Alert”, 1984-1986 (Box 2:, Folder 94)
    - 135 Broad Street: building bids, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 95)
    - Organizations and Operations Study report, 1966 (Box 2:, Folder 96)
    - Personnel evaluation, undated (Box 2:, Folder 97)
    - Personnel policy, undated (Box 2:, Folder 98)
    - Personnel policies: job classifications, 1980-1982 (Box 2:, Folder 99)
    - Personnel salary survey, 1986 (Box 2:, Folder 100)
    - Policies and regulations, 1976-1977 (Box 2:, Folder 101)
    - Retirement Fund, undated (Box 2:, Folder 102)
    - Savings and Security Plan certificate, undated (Box 2:, Folder 103)
    - Secretary Book, 1911-1917 (Box 2:, Folder 104)
    - Special Board of Directors meeting, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 105)
    - Staff calendar, 1977 (Box 2:, Folder 106)
    - Staff directives, undated (Box 2:, Folder 107)
    - Staff Holiday party, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 108)
    - Staff manual, undated (Box 2:, Folder 109)
    - Staff manual, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder 110)
    - Staff, professional: memoranda, undated (Box 2:, Folder 111)
    - Teenage theatre, 1964-1965 (Box 2:, Folder 112)
    - U.S. Department of the Treasury, 1936-1959 (Box 2:, Folder 113)
    - Volunteer development, 1982 (Box 2:, Folder 114)
    - Volunteer Task Force, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder 115)
    - Wangum Lodge, undated (Box 3:, Folder 116)
    - West Hartford Building Dedication, 1957 (Box 3:, Folder 117)
    - Wilfred Academy, undated (Box 3:, Folder 118)
    - Workfare, undated (Box 3:, Folder 119)
    - Zoning: new building, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 120)
  - Subseries B: Branch, undated, 1955-1980
    - East Branch, ?-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 121)
    - East Hartford, undated (Box 3:, Folder 122-124)
    - Eastern Hills, undated (Box 3:, Folder 125)
    - Manchester, 1955-1966 (Box 3:, Folder 126-127)
    - Manchester/Nutmeg, undated (Box 3:, Folder 128)
    - Nutmeg, undated (Box 3:, Folder 129)
    - Scantic, undated (Box 3:, Folder 130)
    - Southwest, undated (Box 3:, Folder 131)
    - Valley West, undated (Box 3:, Folder 132-133)
    - Valley West budget hearing, 1980 (Box 3:, Folder 134)
    - West, undated (Box 3:, Folder 135)
    - West branch, undated (Box 3:, Folder 136)
  - Subseries D: Historical, undated, 1867-1969
    - Ann Street, 1917-1958 (Box 3:, Folder 137-138)
    - The Branch Lantern, undated (Box 3:, Folder 139)
    - Community Chest, 1924 (Box 3:, Folder 140)
    - Conerstone contents: Ann Street building, undated (Box 3:, Folder 141)
    - Correspondence, 1920-1939 (Box 3:, Folder 142)
    - Early residence negatives, undated (Box 3:, Folder 143)
    - Hartford County YWCA, undated (Box 3:, Folder 144)
    - Historical information, undated (Box 3:, Folder 145)
    - Historical research committee data, undated (Box 3:, Folder 146)
    - History, undated (Box 3:, Folder 147)
    - Histories, 1913-1955 (Box 3:, Folder 148-149)
    - Membership form and residence announcement, 1867 (Box 3:, Folder 150)
    - Historical, undated (Box 3:, Folder 151)
    - Officers: Board members, 1914-1969 (Box 3:, Folder 152)
    - Old building, undated (Box 3:, Folder 153)
    - Printed programs, undated (Box 3:, Folder 154)
    - 75 Years A-Growing, 1867-1942 (Box 3:, Folder 155)
    - Woolverton Hall, 1918, 1925 (Box 3:, Folder 156)
  - Subseries E: Finance, 1871-1924
    - Cash book, 1871-1901 (Box 3:, Folder 157)
    - Finance committee reports, 1913-1924 (Box 3:, Folder 158)
    - Ledger book, 1872-1902 (Box 3:, Folder 159)
  - Subseries F: Statistics, 1955-1986
    - 1955-1962 (Box 3:, Folder 160)
    - 1972 September - 1973 August (Box 3:, Folder 161)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 162)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 3:, Folder 163)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 3:, Folder 164)
    - 1979-1982 (Box 3:, Folder 165)
    - Branches, 1981 (Box 3:, Folder 166)
    - Hartford, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder 167)
    - Hartford region, 1977-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 168)
    - Manchester: Time Out for Parents, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder 169)
    - Manchester, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder 170)
    - National
      - 1977-1978 (Box 4:, Folder 171)
      - 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 172)
      - 1983 (Box 4:, Folder 173)
      - 1984 (Box 4:, Folder 174)
      - 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 175)
    - New Britain, 1984-1985 (Box 4:, Folder 176)
    - Profiles, 1982-1984 (Box 4:, Folder 177)
    - Residence, 1966-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 178)
    - Residence, 1980-1982 (Box 4:, Folder 179)
    - Residence, 1983-1984 (Box 4:, Folder 180)
    - Sexual Assault Crises Service, 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 181)
  - Subseries G: Public Relations, undated, 1973-1988
    - Awards programs, undated (Box 5:, Folder 182)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 5:, Folder 183-184)
    - Building News, undated (Box 5:, Folder 185)
    - Centennial Dinner program, undated (Box 5:, Folder 186)
    - Certificates, undated (Box 5:, Folder 187)
    - Connecticut Architect, undated (Box 5:, Folder 188)
    - Executive Director: Brochure, undated (Box 5:, Folder 189)
    - Interchange, undated (Box 5:, Folder 190)
    - Invitations, undated (Box 5:, Folder 191)
    - Marketing, undated (Box 5:, Folder 192)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 5:, Folder 193)
    - News releases, undated (Box 5:, Folder 194)
    - 120 Years Celebration, undated (Box 5:, Folder 195)
    - Outreach, undated (Box 5:, Folder 196)
    - Paste up, undated (Box 5:, Folder 197)
    - Photos, undated (Box 5:, Folder 198)
    - Policies, procedures, forms, undated (Box 5:, Folder 199)
    - Program catalogs, undated (Box 5:, Folder 200-202)
    - Program listings, undated (Box 5:, Folder 203)
    - Record: “Women on the Move” Service spots, undated (Box 5:, Folder 204)
    - The Hartford Courant and Connecticut Woman, undated (Box 5:, Folder 205)
    - Triangle: business, undated (Box 5:, Folder 206)
    - Women in Leadership winners, undated (Box 5:, Folder 207)
    - YWCA Triangle, 1973-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 208)
    - YWCA Triangle, 1979-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 209)
  - Subseries H: Fund Raising, undated, 1944-1982
    - Annual campaign, 1980 (Box 6:, Folder 210)
    - Benefit ideas, undated (Box 6:, Folder 211)
    - Campaign promotion materials, undated (Box 6:, Folder 212)
    - Development, undated (Box 6:, Folder 213)
    - Foundation, undated (Box 6:, Folder 214)
    - Fund Raising Survey, 1967 (Box 6:, Folder 215)
    - George Long Foundation, undated (Box 6:, Folder 216)
    - IRS issues, 1944-1955 (Box 6:, Folder 217)
    - Old Hartford money, undated (Box 6:, Folder 218)
    - Scholarship fund, undated (Box 6:, Folder 219)
    - United Way, 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 220)
    - United Way: Program description, 1981 (Box 6:, Folder 221)
  - Subseries I: Building Campaigns, undated, 1956-1971
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Building, undated (Box 6:, Folder 222)
    - Building campaign material, undated (Box 6:, Folder 223)
    - Building Fund Campaign Committee, undated (Box 6:, Folder 224)
    - Building Fund: Manchester, undated (Box 6:, Folder 225)
    - “Building News”, undated (Box 6:, Folder 226)
    - Building plan, undated (Box 6:, Folder 227)
    - Consultation meeting, 1971 (Box 6:, Folder 228)
    - Mail campaign, undated (Box 6:, Folder 229)
    - YM/YWCA Building Fund campaign, 1956-1957 (Box 6:, Folder 230)
    - YM/YWCA Committee, undated (Box 6:, Folder 231)
- Series II: Minutes, undated, 1867-1985
  - Annual meetings, 1867-1973 (Box 7)
  - Annual meeting, 1983-1985 (Box 8)
  - Board meetings, 1886-1897
  - Board meetings, 1911-1918
  - Board meetings, 1920-1928
  - Board meetings, 1933-1952
  - Board of Directors, 1937-1955; (22 folders)
  - Board of Directors, 1955-1985; (29 folders) (Box 9)
  - Budget Committee, undated
  - Building and Property committee, 1967-1977
  - Camp committee, undated
  - Executive meetings (v. I), 1901-1909
  - Executive meetings (v. II), 1909-1914 (Box 10)
  - Executive meetings (v. III), 1914-1918
  - Executive meetings, 1913-1914 (Box 11)
  - Executive meetings, 1914-1916
  - Executive meetings, 1917-1926
  - Friendship club, 1916-1923
  - Finance committee, 1958-1960
  - Finance committee, 1961-1963
  - Finance committee, 1964-1965
  - Finance committee, 1965
  - Finance committee, 1970-1984
  - HPER, 1970-1976
  - Hartford Program Center committee, 1981-1983
  - Human Resources committee, 1982-1983
  - Investment Advisory committee, 1980-1983
  - Manager's meetings, 1898-1910
  - Membership committee, 1969
  - Other Meetings, 1868-1897
  - Other committee meetings, 1921-1931
  - Program and Services committee, 1982
  - Public Affairs committee, 1978-1982
  - Public Affairs committee, 1978-1982; (3 folders)
  - Race Relations committee, 1926-1934
  - Residence committee, 1979-1980
  - Special Projects committee, 1974-1975
  - Steering committee, 1971
  - Strategic Planning committee, 1982
  - Teen Women's committee, 1975-1976
  - Trustee's meetings, 1920-1925
  - YM/YWCA Joint committee, 1982
- Series III: Committees, undated, 1965-1987
  - Action Audit Implementation, undated (Box 12)
  - Ad Hoc Structure, 1966
  - Affirmative Action, undated
  - Architectural Contract: new building, 1971
  - Building and Property: Ad Hoc, High Hopes, undated
  - Building and Property: Camp, undated
  - Building and Property: Members, undated
  - By-Laws, undated
  - Capital Region Rape Crisis Steering, undated
  - Community/Corporate Day Care Advisory, undated
  - Creative Arts, undated
  - Customer Service, 1985-1987; (2 folders)
  - Dedication: new building, 1974
  - Development, undated; (2 folders)
  - Elimination of Racism, undated
  - Facilities and Property, undated
  - Finance, undated; (2 folders)
  - Hartford Long Range Planning, 1972
  - Health Protection Services (HPS), undated
  - Human Sexuality Sub-committee, undated
  - Inventory Advisory, undated
  - Joint Study, undated
  - Membership, 1970-1984; (4 folders)
  - New building, 1969-1971
  - Nominating, undated; (2 folders)
  - Personnel, 1964-1966, 1982; (2 folders)
  - Program, 1972-1975, 1982
  - Program planning, 1971-1976
  - Public Affairs, 1979, 1981-1982; (2 folders)
  - Public Affairs: Lesbian issues, undated
  - Public Affairs Program, undated
  - Public Policy, undated
  - Public Relations, undated
  - Religious Education, undated
  - Residence, 1965-1973
  - Search, undated
  - Social Responsibility Task Force, 1986
  - Steering, undated; (2 folders)
  - Transportation/Public Affairs, undated
  - Volunteer Development, undated
  - Volunteer Structure Recommendation, undated
  - West Hartford Joint YM/YWCA, undated
  - Women's Physical Fitness Center (WPFC), undated
  - Women's Issues, undated
- Series IV: Residence Records, undated, 1967-1982
  - Ad Hoc committee, 1967-1971 (Box 13)
  - Ann Street, undated; (2 folders)
  - Budget, 1982
  - Charter Oak Place: Correspondence, 1972-1973
  - Field placement, 1971
  - Interim residence, 1971
  - Louver project, 1980
  - Memoranda, 1980
  - Minutes, 1971-1981; (4 folders)
  - Minutes: Food Service, undated
  - New building, 1970-1973